hi i'm dennis ing
chief revenue officer of sme ecosystem
in prudential
and i'm edmund lim i'm the chief
partnership officer
in the ecosystem for prudential i run
the sme ecosystem in potential so the
idea of the sme consisted of prudential
is to make sure that we serve
a very large underserved segment in asia
and africa and
also what i want to do is level the
playing field between
a small company and a large company to
provide them the right tools providing
the right solutions
make sure that they're empowered to do
their business and grow their business
so at prudential we are
embarking on a very ambitious digital
strategy
we want to engage with our customers
more proactively now
through digital means and we do that by
making them
healthier and wealthier through our app
pulse
and we can't do that all by ourselves we
bring partners in with
special capabilities that will help us
engage
with our users and build a better
relationship with them
i think the the nimbleness of hr easily
was very appealing and also the
innovations that they created over the
hr tools and
the way they manage their business is
very interesting and also very
progressive
it was a no-brainer for us because they
had
a lot of smes already on their platform
so it kind of
confirms that they have something that
we should have as well
and so we brought them in the good part
about hr is
the real good thing is the willingness
to go all out with us
because the sme market is a it's a
challenging although underserved market
but i think
as uh hisd has always been very
forthcoming i think hr easily
although their startup they also
understand how to work with large
corporates like us
and they are flexible and nimble like
what dennis said
to accommodate our different needs and
at the same time i find that a lot of
their solutions are quite forward
looking and forward thinking and that
will definitely
be a plus for our customers
[Music]
so the the reason why we want to work
with hrisd as a distribution partner was
one of the key reasons is to reach out
to a portfolio of customers that we
would never have anyway so so i think in
the hrc's reach into the sme market is
very deep as of now
so we are leveraging on their strengths
as well for us
we look at hr easily as an ecosystem
partner so
we are building an ecosystem together so
it makes sense
for us to enhance this ecosystem by
selling each other's products
and so while on one hand we are selling
hr is these business to
our customers at the same time we see a
great opportunity for hr easy to sell
our products to their customers and you
know given their large customer base is
a very exciting opportunity for us
and beyond we are customers the
corporates
we are also looking to see how we can
better serve
the employees as well and protect their
lives and that of their families
[Music]
with history the co-creation of product
sets and insurance solutions is a very
key
component of this partnership because it
allows us to also
get closer to the customers and allows
us to understand sma customers better
because of
hr easily's experience with smes so we
need to find
new angles new ways to connect with the
customers and
hr easily brings a new dimension because
they know what employees need you know
just a general trend
about this health concerns
like diabetes or also hypertension
which we see rising and so we want to
straight away
go and support these set of
people who will need insurance most and
we see hr easily as a partner for us to
be able to
offer this kind of help and solutions to
this customer market on that note right
partnering with hrc actually provides
us also the extra lens that we never had
because we are super good at uh
individual customers
but we are we are just getting there in
terms of enterprises
we probably have some elements of
artificial intelligence inside there
because now now ai and also
biometrics and all that it's probably
going to be part of the hr tech
that you see it evolving over the next
few years there'll be strong usage of
artificial intelligence i will see
in the next three to five years i think
the pandemic has taught us that
just having physical hr individuals in
the office may not be sufficient
it cannot be everywhere we serve
everyone
and so we think hr tools to be able to
remotely serve
anyone working from anywhere will be
increasingly important
and the responsiveness of these tools is
also equally important and that's where
i see
forward thinking companies like hr easy
feeling